[Music]
Those who have crossed all limits for the country,
why should there be any Sharad in the country for them
[Music]
[Praise]
[Music] Those who
are deployed day and night for our security,
we should also be with them in their need
[Music]
For whom we all are their own After all,
they too have some dreams for their loved ones
Whose bravery we all are indebted to It is
our duty too to encourage their progress
[Music] Those
whose life is tougher than ours
Perhaps they also like a little comfort in their normal life Because of
whose presence this sky, land
and water are safe It is our duty too to secure
their today and
tomorrow ICICI Defence Salary Account
with super benefits Special for our Super Heroes
i